OLEKSII BARDYSHEV

Frontend Developer

ABOUT

I'm a software developer with more than a year of experience in frontend development. I have over 500 hours of coding, and 100+ completed tasks using React, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5/CSS3/SASS, and BEM. I have a strong base of technical knowledge in Redux, Node.js, ES6, Git, NPM, Bootstrap, JSON, and Web API. I'm also willing to learn Python and new frameworks.

I'm captivated by web technology and constantly trying to learn something new or learn more about what is already known to me about the web.

Experience in digital strategy and television has helped me manage to do lots of things at once, resolve any conflicts in the team, and time management.

I'm an AI art and creative coding lover.

WORK EXPERIENCE



2022 (6 months)

Frontend Developer

Training projects, Feb 2022 - Present

Technologies: JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, BEM See some of my projects at:

Landing page for Kiskctarter

- <u>Demo</u>
- <u>GitHub Code</u>

Landing page for MET

- Demo
- GitHub Code



ught 2015 - 2022 (7 years 1 month)

Head of Group of Digital Strategy and Content Making

Novy Channel, Jan 2019 - May 2022

Responsibilities:

- Managing the team of creators, movie makers and editors
- Generating ideas for new content (shows, TV-series, YouTube), sponsorship and creative campaigns

Key accomplishments:

As a Digital Strategy Specialist collaborated with such brands as:

- Coca-cola coverage of ad campaign is more than 1 000 000 (12% more compared to coverage forecast)
- UNICEF campaign BreaktheFake has 600 000 views on YouTube (it's 48% more compared to average)
- Nescafé campaign coverage is more than 700 000

CONTACT

+38 099 36 11 306



bardyshev@gmail.com

@oleksiibardyshev <u>Oleksii Bardyshev</u>

in

github.com/alexbardyshev



Kyiv, Ukraine



Ready to work remotely

SKILLS

Web technologies:

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Sass(SCSS), DOM, Bootstrap, Fetch, REST API

Frameworks & Libraries:

React (React router, React hooks), Redux (React-redux)

Methodologies:

Pixel-perfect, BEM, Adaptive and cross-browser layout

Tools:

Git & GitHub, Chrome & React DevTools, NPM, Eslint, VSCode

Design Tools:

Figma, Photoshop

Time management Tools:

Trello, Notion, Jira

<u>Agile:</u>

Kanban/Scrum

Basic OOP understanding, basic Python knowledge



English: Advanced

- Lay's 24 000 new subscribers in Instagram during a month of collaboration
- Ukrainian Fashion Week 22% more views of live stream compared to the previous season

As a showrunner created TV-series for Novy Channel during quarantine with more than 3 mln of views on YouTube

O Head of Digital Department of "Kyiv Day and Night"

Novy Channel, Aug 2015 - Dec 2018

Responsibilities:

- Managing the team of content-creators
- Generating ideas for sponsorship and creative campaigns

Key accomplishment:

More than 500 000 of subscribers on Instagram in one year

O Head of Digital Strategy for SWEDEN-UKRAINE **BUSINESS FORUM**

Embassy of Sweden in Ukraine, Mar 2018 - Jun 2018 Responsibilities:

• Managing the team of SMM-managers and content creators

O Head of Digital Strategy for KERUI PROJECT

National Police of Ukraine, Oct 2017 - Dec 2017 Responsibilities:

• Managing the team of SMM-managers and web-site developers

Key accomplishment:

• Coverage of this digital campaign was more than 5 mln

1+1 2014 - 2015 (8 months)

O Editor/Scriptwriter of "The Voice" talent-show

TV-channel 1+1, May 2014 - Jan 2015

Responsibilities:

- · Writing scripts for the show
- Interview participants and judges during the shooting process



2010 - 2014 (4 years 3 months)

O Reporter of entertainment news

STB TV-channel, Feb 2010 - May 2014

Responsibilities:

- Interview celebrities
- Making reports from film presentations and concerts

Key accomplishment:

• I interviewed more than 100 of Ukrainian and world celebrities

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in English, Foreign literature and History

Horlivka State Pedagogical Institute of Foreign Languages

2003 - 2008

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Fullstack course at Mate Academy (Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Web)
- Udemy course: The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp
- Udemy course: 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2022
- Domestika course: Creative Coding: Making Visuals with JavaScript
- CodeWars [4 Kata Completed]
- CS50's Introduction to Computer Science

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I was part of the StarLight Media marketing team that won gold at the Effie awards as the Best Marketing Team 2020
- Videos produced by my teams have more than 100 mIn of views
- I have more than 68K subscribers on TikTok with more than 2,4 mln of likes
- Typing speed 50-55 WPM